Wh-What'd they say?
(Howard:)Uh, it's basically
a summary of the theory,
(Howard:)but there's a bunch of positive
comments on the message board.
(Leonard:)Let me see,
let me see.
One calls it "insightful
and innovative."
(Leonard:)We're insightful
and innovative.
Ooh, nice to meet you,
Mr. Insightful.
(Leonard:)Oh, the pleasure is mine,
Mr. Innovative.
(Leonard:)Uh, another one says,
"The concept shows
(Leonard:)some real out-of-the-box
thinking."
(Leonard:)Do you hear that,
Mr. Out-Of-The?
(Sheldon:)I do, indeed,
Mr. Box-Thinking.
(Howard:)How are you today,
(Howard:)Mr. Can-You-Believe-
These-Jack-Asses?
(Raj:)Just dandy, Mr....
(Raj:)I-Wish-I-Was-
Better-At-Improv.
(Sheldon:)Read another one.
Okay, okay. Uh...
"The analogy
between space-time
(Leonard:)and a supercooled fluid is
either meaningless or... false."
"I wish this blog would
devote itself to real science
"instead of wasting
our time with crackpot,
(Leonard:)wannabe theoreticians
in a rush to publish."
(Sheldon:)Who wrote that?
(Leonard:)It's anonymous,
(Leonard:)and user name
"General Relativity."